<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="schedule.xsl"?>
<schedule>
	<day id="1">
		<date>September 26th, 2014</date>
		<weekday>Friday</weekday>
		<slot id="1">Evening 7:00 pm to 11:00 pm - Free admission Friday night</slot>
	</day>
	<day id="2">
		<date>March 25th, 2017</date>
		<weekday>Saturday</weekday>
		<slot id="4">Evening 8:00 pm to 12:00 pm</slot>
		<slot id="3">Afternoon 3:00 pm to 7:00 pm</slot>
		<slot id="2">Morning 10:00 am to 2:00 pm</slot>
		<note dayid="2">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
                <b>Phantasm Yard Sale the Details:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Bring in your stuff &amp; we’ll sell it for you while you play.</li>
                    <li>Yard Sale we be open from noon on Sat until 5pm on Sunday.</li>
                    <li>You must have a list of what you are selling, with all of the prices on the items along with your initials (I’d suggest using stickers for this). All prices must be rounded to the nearest whole dollar.</li>
                    <li>Phantasm holds no responsibility for the items (though we will have someone there &amp; no-one has ever stolen anything from a table), has the right to opt not to sell an item, and will keep 10% of the value of the items sold.</li>
                </ul>]]>
			</desc>
		</note>
	</day>
	<day id="3">
		<date>March 26th, 2017</date>
		<weekday>Sunday</weekday>
		<slot id="6">Afternoon 3:00 pm to 7:00 pm</slot>
		<slot id="5">Morning 10:00 am to 2:00 pm</slot>
		<note dayid="3">
			<desc></desc>
		</note>
	</day>
	<games>
		<game slot="2" id="1">
			<name>Metro City Blues</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="29">James K</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[More "Cobrai Kai" than "Crouching Tiger", Metro City Blues is about frail heroes in a desperate world, throwing punches, throwing kicks, throwing away their lives. This is gritty, a little cheesy, indie RPG about martial artists in a city covered in neon. A Cyberpunk without the technology. Based on 80s action films like Jean Claude Van Damme´s "Bloodsport", and video games like "Final Fight", explore underground gambling dens, biker bars, dojos, and heartache. The rules are easy to learn and taught at the table. If you´re looking for a different role-playing experience, this is the chosen one. No retreat. No surrender.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="2">
			<name>Scum and Villainy</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="19">Erik W.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You are the crew of the hyperdrive smuggling ship Torqued Tesseract and you are in trouble. Again. Your most trusted business partners have you at blaster point. One of you, according to them, is actually a cleverly disguised android carrying a warp bomb, programmed to think its a member of the crew. You´re going to be bundled into a cargo boat and taken to a secure location where you can be "safely dismantled." All of you. For safety´s sake. Is this the end of the TT? Try this new space opera system from the makers of "Blades in the Dark" and see if you can save your crew. Or yourself.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="3">
			<name>The Spy Who Foiled Me</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="118">Richard B.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Something very important was stolen from The Agency and you need to get it back, but you only have a single lead.  You will be tasked with infiltrating secure areas, charming unsuspecting marks, and eliminating choice obstacles as you pursue a mission that will determine the fate of intelligence operations across the globe. The Spy who Foiled Me is a stealth and intrigue RPG that tries to recreate the cinematic experiences found in James Bond, Kingsmen, HITMAN, and many other franchises within the spy genre. Build your own character and get ready to leave you mark as a silent assassin or to the fanfare of explosions as you embark on this adventure!´]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="4">
			<name>Call of Cthulhu</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="26">Ian M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Hard Vacuum]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You´ve been working the Kuiper Belt for years, one of the best freelance Zero-G mining outfits in the outer rim. It wasn´t a surprise when one of the wealthiest men in the system requested you by name, but it was odd he wanted to tag along. They say money and eccentricity go hand-in-hand, and he´s paying you enough that he´s welcome to be as weird as he likes. He still gives you the creeps, though... Hard Vaccum is a Call of Cthulhu (7e) scenario for 4-6 players. Pre-generated characters provided. Contains mature/disturbing content.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="5">
			<name>Fantasy Trip</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="6">Chris C.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Steve Jackson’s re-release of The Fantasy Trip allows people to game once more like it’s 1979. The adventure is King Kamehameha’s Curse, a Polynesian and Tiki inspired island adventure. Your party must return an amulet to the shrine caves of King Kamehameha to lift the curse of a guilt ridden trader and former adventurer, who founded his fortune by leaving his old party to its doom. Returning the quartz amulet will be easy. Exiting the caves of King Kamehameha and his creepy, watery denizens will not prove so easy. 4-6 players. No experience necessary. Tiki mugs and cocktail umbrellas provided.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="6">
			<name>Shadowrun 6th ed.</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="31">Jason M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Extortion Racket]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The daughter of a corporate executive has been abducted and is being held for ransom.  Unable to pay the demanded sum, the company instead opts for a clandestine operation, hiring the runners to track down and rescue the young woman before any harm comes to her.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="7">
			<name>Tiny Wasteland</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="117">Terry B.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[TinyD6 gets apocalyptic! The versatile and minimalist TinyD6 ruleset hits the road in this post-apocalyptic sourcebook. Containing new rules for settlements, vehicles, and mutations, Tiny Wastelands is your trust companion in the blasted landscapes of the near-future.<br />Powered by the TinyD6 engine, with streamlined mechanics that utilize only one to three single six-sided dice on every action, characters that can be written 3x5 notecard, and easy to  understand and teach rules, Tiny Wastelands is here to be your rules-lite waypoint on your lonely apocalyptic road!]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="8">
			<name>Paranoia</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="130">Rob H</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="9">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="131">Jason Mel.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[CCC-GHC-BK1-07 The Peculiar Case of the Selptan Felines]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Well that’s odd. There sure are a lot of cats in the hamlet of Selpt. In fact, it seems as if just about everyone has one, and boy do they pamper those cats. Even if you’ve never been a cat person, it’s hard to say no. In fact, you should probably be adopted by one straight away. Yes, that’s it. You belong to that cat. Who’s a pretty human?<br /><br />A Two-Hour to Four-Hour Adventure for Tier 1 Characters]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="10">
			<name>Fate (core)</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="39">Justin L.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Halloween Hunt (Dresdin Files)]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The graveyards in Peterborough have been vandalized, the local PD have called in the cities only occult experts to translate the weird symbols and drawings found at the graves. The nights have become cold and an eerie wind blows, dogs howl in fear and the city has an undertone of eldritch silence. Can the detectives at “Mystic wonders” discover what is happening? Or will this Halloween claim more than candy from its citizens?]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="11">
			<name>Mutants and Masterminds Second Edition</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="82">Sean M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Call me trouble !]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[WARNING:  this game is not approved for children or young adults. Game will include adult themes, ultra violence and subject matter. <br />The suicide squad is baffled at Waller this time. It’s not every day she dispatches the lot to goto a small shop in Central City. What in the world does Morts Mysterious Merchandise have in store for them this time.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="12">
			<name>Tales from the Loop</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="37">Jordan G.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Creatures from the Cretaceous]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Winter holds it´s icy grip over a quiet Canadian Town in the 1980s. The Kids search for a missing dog for a hefty reward, but strange beasts have been spotted in the woods, and a skiier has gone missing. Can the Kids put a stop to this time-mixed mystery? Or will this be the Final Countdown to a blast from the past?<br /><br />Tales From The Loop is a rpg that brings out the kid in you as you explore a nostalgia tinted 1980s where things are a little stranger than you remember.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="13">
			<name>Hero Clixs</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="115">Dave C.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Based on the popular Mage Knights system, but utilizing super hero characters from the Marvel and DC Comics Universe.<br /><br />The game plays much like a miniatures game, but without the measure-and-move system or the constant consultation of hit charts. Rather, most of the vital statistical information is directly on the base of the characters, which can be rotated as characters take damage from hits.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="2" id="14">
			<name>Arcadia Quest</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="70">Trevor L.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Board Game]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Arcadia Quest is a campaign-based game for 2 to 4 players, where each player controls a guild of three unique heroes, facing off against the other players and the various monsters controlled by the game. Players need to accomplish a series of quests in order to win each scenario and choose where to go next in the campaign.<br /><br />Players are able to choose the path their campaign takes, navigating through six out of eleven available scenarios, so each time the campaign is played it can have a different configuration of scenarios. As the campaign progresses, the heroes are able to acquire new weapons, equipment and abilities that give them powerful options to tackle the obstacles ahead. Furthermore, by fulfilling specific quests in a scenario, players unlock exclusive features in subsequent scenarios.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="15">
			<name>Fate of the Norns</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="29">James K</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Lo, for you are vikings living in Ragnarok, the end times. Three years ago wolves devoured the sun and moon. The world dwells in darkness and perpetual winter, awaiting the final battle that will end all. Before that happens, however, there are still battles to be fought and treasures won. Who dares risk all to see out the end days in luxury? The RPG system of "Fate of the Norns: Ragnarok" uses the drawing of runes instead of dice rolls. It´s  easy to learn and intuitive in practice. New players make the best vikings! As a Phantasm treat, this game will include sneak-peak content from the "Horn of the Kraken" adventure module set for release next year.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="16">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="5">Bryan M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Smurfy Adventure]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Life is going well in the Smurfs new mountain keep, good times for all.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="17">
			<name>Pathfinder 2nd Ed.</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="132">Denis H.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Lastwall has fallen to the undead and orc hordes. The survivors of Lastwall retreat but a select few are chosen to move forward. A daring mission to recover a relic from an ancient ruin before the evil hordes claim it. A Pathfinder 2nd ed introduction game for players of all experience levels.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="18">
			<name>Call of Cthulhu</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="26">Ian M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Boil Water Advisory]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The posters went up this morning, there´s a council meeting tonight. Water´s bad. Again. No doubt the men from Duarock will be singing their same old song. They think because they employ a good chunk of the settlment that we owe them an audience. I wouldn´t be surprised if they had something to do with the water. Tempers are smouldering.. all it would take is one small spark. Boil Water Advisoet is a Call of Cthulhu (7e) scenario for 4-6 players. Pre-generated characters provided. Contains mature/disturbing content.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="19">
			<name>Arcadia Quest</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="70">Trevor L.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Board Game]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Arcadia Quest is a campaign-based game for 2 to 4 players, where each player controls a guild of three unique heroes, facing off against the other players and the various monsters controlled by the game. Players need to accomplish a series of quests in order to win each scenario and choose where to go next in the campaign.<br /><br />Players are able to choose the path their campaign takes, navigating through six out of eleven available scenarios, so each time the campaign is played it can have a different configuration of scenarios. As the campaign progresses, the heroes are able to acquire new weapons, equipment and abilities that give them powerful options to tackle the obstacles ahead. Furthermore, by fulfilling specific quests in a scenario, players unlock exclusive features in subsequent scenarios.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="20">
			<name>5e Modern (WWII)</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="85">Alec M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Suit up as a member of the 1st Canadian Parachute Battalion as they undertake one of the most daring missions of World War 2: Operation Overlord.<br />You are a soldier in "B" company. Your mission is simple: Destroy a key bridge to prevent a German counter-attack, and hold the area against all attackers. It is a do or die operation, but your advanced training in heavy weapons, field craft, demolitions, and survival will give you the edge you need to succeed. The fate of Europe hangs in the balance. Will you do you do your duty?<br /><br /> This is a rules-light historical homebrew based on the D&D 5e Ruleset.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="21">
			<name>Transformers RPG</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="57">John P.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Transformers RPG is a fan made game by James Kerr that allows players to make up their own transformer… is that a wolf deploying fleas equipped with missiles… and will be divided into two teams the Autobots or Deceptions. A scenario will be provided and each team will have their own mission to complete using their proper programming. Players must roll play their character with the proper assigned (Autobot/Decepticon) programming. For example, an Autobot would be inclined to negotiate to the local government for energy access while a Decepticon would rather break into the local power plant, convert every scrap of energy into energon cubes and leave nothing left but a smoking ruin, burnt and melted beyond all hope of repair.<br /><br />This is a quick and easy game to learn. The game uses a d10 base system for decision making and a d6 for damage. Dice will be provided if players lack their own.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="22">
			<name>7th Seas 2nd ed.</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="31">Jason M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Pirates of the South Seas]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Their business concluded in the Crescent Empire, the Heroes are able to set sail aboard their recently acquired Crescent Brigantine.  Escorting a merchant ship through pirate-filled waters pays well, but the Heroes find themselves embroiled in a larger pirate plot.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="23">
			<name>Elemental</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="55">Steve C.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[The World´s End Masque and Ball]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You are cordially invited...<br /><br /><br />Some say the world is ending. At the muddy end of a fruitless harvest, famine and plague stalk the land. The armies of darkness gather on the horizon. And tonight is the night of a lunar eclipse, the time when the astrologers predict a world-devouring evil will be born.<br /><br />For one group of decadent aristocrats, there is clearly only one possible course of action: lock themselves inside a castle, throw a masquerade, get loaded, and dabble in black magic.<br /><br />For a group of desperate adventurers, the masquerade is a chance to set things right. But on a night like this, they may get more than they bargained for.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="24">
			<name>Elemental</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="122">Wil</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Fear Can´t Hurt You]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[In August of 1984, the FBI investigated the events at Camp Willow Lake, a Christian summer camp for boys. Multiple deaths were reported in the press, but the circumstances surrounding the fate of the campers and staff remains a mystery. This is their story.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="25">
			<name>Monster of the Week</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="133">Dave G.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Hunt For the Thessalhydra is a new adventure written from the perspective of the kids from Stranger Things but rather than playing as Fighters or Wizards, what if you were The Chosen One like Buffy or the Winchester brothers or someone from the X-Files? Find out how they react to The Upside-down and see if you can complete the quest.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="26">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="97">Derek M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="27">
			<name>Solar Blades &amp; Cosmic Spells</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="37">Jordan G.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Skull Prison, the one place in the Universe where Hell would be preferable. This dank, cruel and desolate satellite is escape-proof, and built to squeeze every bit of hope from it´s prisoners before their eventual untimely death. In short, it´s the perfect place for the Galactic Overlords to place their enemies.<br /><br />For whatever reason, you´ve all found yourselves hopeless prisoners, but when the power fails, one chance unveils itself.<br />One chance to escape.<br /><br />Will you work together to take it? Or will you die in agony on the prison floor?<br /><br />Solar Blades & Cosmic Spells is a Sharp Swords & Sinister Spells (SS&SS) based game that pulls it´s inspiration from Heavy Metal, Thundarr The Barbarian, She-Ra/He-Man, Rocket Robinhood and others like it. Blast through the Galaxy in your trusty ship, play with fire with the Sorcery/Psychic powers of the Galaxy, and show the Galactic Overlords something to be afraid of.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="28">
			<name>Hero Clixs</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="115">Dave C.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Based on the popular Mage Knights system, but utilizing super hero characters from the Marvel and DC Comics Universe.<br /><br />The game plays much like a miniatures game, but without the measure-and-move system or the constant consultation of hit charts. Rather, most of the vital statistical information is directly on the base of the characters, which can be rotated as characters take damage from hits.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="29">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="119">Nathan D.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[My pleasure is to run for the players a massive 3d printed and foam dungeon for a 5th edition Dungeons and Dragons module.  This module put the players / characters to break out of a necromancer’s jail.  The players character has nothing in common but secrets and have to work together.  This dungeon crawl will be a dungeon craw of epic proportions.   The players/characters have to use their brains, brawn, skill and intelligence to navigate the maze to get out alive or become part of the army of dead.  <br />(each session will include a higher level of characters and will include prizes for completion of various goals.)]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="3" id="30">
			<name>AFMBE</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="39">Justin L.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Live aid 2020]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Once again the music industry has stepped in to help the biggest crisis the world has ever seen. Climate change! In every major city across the world, big name bands will take to the stage for a three day music festival with free admission. The catch, all proceeds will be given to charity science organizations with one goal, R&D for the future. <br /><br />The Dawn alliance foundation has funded all music sites in North America and provided Venus and refreshments for attendees and acts. You and your friends have made the trip up to the Molson amphitheater in Toronto. You gather pledges from Peterborough and have taken the laborious ride up the 401 to enjoy this celebration of humanity. <br /><br />Did the water taste funny to you? Was that hotdog really meat? You don’t feel so well Day 2 and others seem to have fallen ill. Maybe it’s the weather...<br /><br />A human survival game set in the universe of Eden games All Flesh must be eaten setting.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="31">
			<name>Call of Cthulhu</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="5">Bryan M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Murder in Kingsport]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Captain Holt, one of the eldest residents of Kingsport has been murdered. It is up to the Kingsport PD to find the killers and bring them to justice.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="32">
			<name>Pathfinder 2nd Ed.</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="132">Denis H.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Lastwall has fallen to the undead and orc hordes. The survivors of Lastwall retreat but a select few are chosen to move forward. A daring mission to recover a relic from an ancient ruin before the evil hordes claim it. A Pathfinder 2nd ed introduction game for players of all experience levels.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="33">
			<name>Feegle</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="109">Kerri F.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[The Wee Free Men a Feegle adventure]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Nac Mac Feegles are back!  Things have been quiet around the Feegle mound.  The boys have been annoying their Kelda in their boredom, so they have decided to go adventuring (it´s safer).  Big Willy and his brothers have decided to visit the Unseen University Library again.  What will happen this time?  Crazy shenanigans is guaranteed but other than that all bets are off.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="34">
			<name>Call of Cthulhu</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="26">Ian M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Bloody Ballot]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[It´s election time in Arkham! Unfortunately, having no fixed address, you´re ineligible to vote. Worse, the leading candidate seems to be campaigning on running unfortunates like you, and others who don´t meet their "community" standards, out of town. Worst of all, you think someone might be acting on that rhetoric. People have been disappearing from the riverfront, some of them your friends. How long until they come for you? Bloody Ballot is a Call of Cthulhu (7e) scenario for 4-6 players. Pre-generated characters provided. Contains mature/disturbing content.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="35">
			<name>Fantasy Trip</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="6">Chris C.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Steve Jackson’s re-release of The Fantasy Trip allows people to game once more like it’s 1979. The adventure is King Kamehameha’s Curse, a Polynesian and Tiki inspired island adventure. Your party must return an amulet to the shrine caves of King Kamehameha to lift the curse of a guilt ridden trader and former adventurer, who founded his fortune by leaving his old party to its doom. Returning the quartz amulet will be easy. Exiting the caves of King Kamehameha and his creepy, watery denizens will not prove so easy. 4-6 players. No experience necessary. Tiki mugs and cocktail umbrellas provided.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="36">
			<name>Scum and Villany</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="19">Erik W.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You are the crew of the hyperdrive smuggling ship Torqued Tesseract and you are in trouble. Again. Your most trusted business partners have you at blaster point. One of you, according to them, is actually a cleverly disguised android carrying a warp bomb, programmed to think its a member of the crew. You´re going to be bundled into a cargo boat and taken to a secure location where you can be "safely dismantled." All of you. For safety´s sake. Is this the end of the TT? Try this new space opera system from the makers of "Blades in the Dark" and see if you can save your crew. Or yourself.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="37">
			<name>The Mountain Witch</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="29">James K</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[It´s "Seven Samurai" meets "Reservoir Dogs" in this tabletop RPG about trust, betrayal, and confronting one´s fate. A group of ronin samurai unknown to each other are hired to climb Mount Fuji and kill the witch that lives at its summit. Yet, each samurai has a secret mission that may work against each other. When every heart holds betrayal, who can you trust? Treat yourself Saturday with this unsung indie RPG darling, with its innovative Trust mechanic and gripping, deadly samurai action.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="38">
			<name>Boardgame Boonanza</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="97">Derek M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Boardgames]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Meeple Party (45 minutes), Dungeon Doodles (20 minutes), The Artemis Project (90 minutes), Imhotep with expansions (45 minutes), Dungeon Mayham (20 minutes), and my favourite classic Kingsburg (90 minutes)]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="39">
			<name>Elemental</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="55">Steve C.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[The World´s End Masque and Ball]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You are cordially invited...<br /><br /><br />Some say the world is ending. At the muddy end of a fruitless harvest, famine and plague stalk the land. The armies of darkness gather on the horizon. And tonight is the night of a lunar eclipse, the time when the astrologers predict a world-devouring evil will be born.<br /><br />For one group of decadent aristocrats, there is clearly only one possible course of action: lock themselves inside a castle, throw a masquerade, get loaded, and dabble in black magic.<br /><br />For a group of desperate adventurers, the masquerade is a chance to set things right. But on a night like this, they may get more than they bargained for.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="40">
			<name>Elemental</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="122">Wil</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Fear Can´t Hurt You]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[In August of 1984, the FBI investigated the events at Camp Willow Lake, a Christian summer camp for boys. Multiple deaths were reported in the press, but the circumstances surrounding the fate of the campers and staff remains a mystery. This is their story.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="41">
			<name>Mutants and Masterminds 2nd ed</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="82">Sean M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Into the Lions Den]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[WARNING:  this game is not approved for children or young adults. Game will include adult themes, ultra violence and subject matter. <br />It’s bad enough Waller is sending the squad to Gotham, with the ever possible bat problem, but this just doesn’t make any sense. What could she possibly want from a loft apartment in the bad part of Gotham?]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="42">
			<name>The Strange (Cypher)</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="37">Jordan G.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[The Curious Case of Tom Mallard]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Being new recruits into the Shadow Agency ´The Estate´ you´ve been tasked with keeping watch on a known Recursion Miner by the name of Tom Mallard. While staking things out, you realise that things are a little too quiet and decide to investigate a little more thoroughly.<br /><br />The Strange is a Cypher System-based game where you play Recursors, people with the special ability to ´translate´ into small pocket dimensions called Recursions, and blend into these many different worlds. If it´s been thought of, it exists out there, somewhere as a Recursion.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="43">
			<name>Hero Clixs</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="115">Dave C.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Based on the popular Mage Knights system, but utilizing super hero characters from the Marvel and DC Comics Universe.<br /><br />The game plays much like a miniatures game, but without the measure-and-move system or the constant consultation of hit charts. Rather, most of the vital statistical information is directly on the base of the characters, which can be rotated as characters take damage from hits.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="4" id="44">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="119">Nathan D.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[My pleasure is to run for the players a massive 3d printed and foam dungeon for a 5th edition Dungeons and Dragons module.  This module put the players / characters to break out of a necromancer’s jail.  The players character has nothing in common but secrets and have to work together.  This dungeon crawl will be a dungeon craw of epic proportions.   The players/characters have to use their brains, brawn, skill and intelligence to navigate the maze to get out alive or become part of the army of dead.  <br />(each session will include a higher level of characters and will include prizes for completion of various goals.)]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="45">
			<name>Metro City Blues</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="29">James K</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[More "Cobrai Kai" than "Crouching Tiger", Metro City Blues is about frail heroes in a desperate world, throwing punches, throwing kicks, throwing away their lives. This is gritty, a little cheesy, indie RPG about martial artists in a city covered in neon. A Cyberpunk without the technology. Based on 80s action films like Jean Claude Van Damme´s "Bloodsport", and video games like "Final Fight", explore underground gambling dens, biker bars, dojos, and heartache. The rules are easy to learn and taught at the table. If you´re looking for a different role-playing experience, this is the chosen one. No retreat. No surrender.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="46">
			<name>Dogs of the Apocalypse</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="109">Kerri F.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Its a while after some form of apocalypse has decimated humankind leaving their beloved pets stranded and fending for themselves.  A pack of dogs get together to try to escape Toronto to find a better life outside the city wasteland.  Will they succeed?  Or fail?  Will the cat´s advice be true and will they find the land of warm hearths and belly rubs?]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="47">
			<name>The Spy Who Foiled Me</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="118">Richard B.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Something very important was stolen from The Agency and you need to get it back, but you only have a single lead.  You will be tasked with infiltrating secure areas, charming unsuspecting marks, and eliminating choice obstacles as you pursue a mission that will determine the fate of intelligence operations across the globe. The Spy who Foiled Me is a stealth and intrigue RPG that tries to recreate the cinematic experiences found in James Bond, Kingsmen, HITMAN, and many other franchises within the spy genre. Build your own character and get ready to leave you mark as a silent assassin or to the fanfare of explosions as you embark on this adventure!´]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="48">
			<name>Call of Cthulhu</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="26">Ian M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Hard Vacuum]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You´ve been working the Kuiper Belt for years, one of the best freelance Zero-G mining outfits in the outer rim. It wasn´t a surprise when one of the wealthiest men in the system requested you by name, but it was odd he wanted to tag along. They say money and eccentricity go hand-in-hand, and he´s paying you enough that he´s welcome to be as weird as he likes. He still gives you the creeps, though... Hard Vaccum is a Call of Cthulhu (7e) scenario for 4-6 players. Pre-generated characters provided. Contains mature/disturbing content.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="49">
			<name>Scum and Villany</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="19">Erik W.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You are the crew of the hyperdrive smuggling ship Torqued Tesseract and you are in trouble. Again. Your most trusted business partners have you at blaster point. One of you, according to them, is actually a cleverly disguised android carrying a warp bomb, programmed to think its a member of the crew. You´re going to be bundled into a cargo boat and taken to a secure location where you can be "safely dismantled." All of you. For safety´s sake. Is this the end of the TT? Try this new space opera system from the makers of "Blades in the Dark" and see if you can save your crew. Or yourself.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="50">
			<name>Shadowrun: Sprawl Ops</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="31">Jason M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Board Game]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Shadowrun: Sprawl Ops is a competitive game for 2 to 4 players that can be played in 60 to 90 minutes. In this cyber-punk worker-placement game, each player controls a team of Shadow Runners that they can send on missions, loan to other players (for a fee, of course), and upgrade with new tech and equipment. Missions are resolved by rolling combinations of custom dice. A diverse team of Shadow Runners gives you access to more combinations of dice, and your upgrades add even more dice to your pool. Take on smaller missions to earn creds. Then, put those right back into more experienced runners, and better gear. Once you think you´ve got what it takes, send your runners out to attempt to collect one final score. If you fail, don´t worry, your doc-wagon contracts will keep your runners in the game. The first player to successfully complete the final mission, and collect that last big score wins the game!]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="51">
			<name>Tiny Wasteland</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="117">Terry B.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[TinyD6 gets apocalyptic! The versatile and minimalist TinyD6 ruleset hits the road in this post-apocalyptic sourcebook. Containing new rules for settlements, vehicles, and mutations, Tiny Wastelands is your trust companion in the blasted landscapes of the near-future.<br />Powered by the TinyD6 engine, with streamlined mechanics that utilize only one to three single six-sided dice on every action, characters that can be written 3x5 notecard, and easy to  understand and teach rules, Tiny Wastelands is here to be your rules-lite waypoint on your lonely apocalyptic road!]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="52">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="131">Jason Mel.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[CCC-UCON-01 Blood & Fog]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Heavy mists have plagued the area around Phlan for weeks, even after the reported death of Vorgansharax, the Maimed Virulence. People have been disappearing in those deadly fogs, and now dead bodies are turning up. A D&D Adventurer’s League adventure set in the Quivering Forest.<br /><br />A 4-hour Adventure for 5th – 10th Level Characters]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="53">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="119">Nathan D.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[My pleasure is to run for the players a massive 3d printed and foam dungeon for a 5th edition Dungeons and Dragons module.  This module put the players / characters to break out of a necromancer’s jail.  The players character has nothing in common but secrets and have to work together.  This dungeon crawl will be a dungeon craw of epic proportions.   The players/characters have to use their brains, brawn, skill and intelligence to navigate the maze to get out alive or become part of the army of dead.  <br />(each session will include a higher level of characters and will include prizes for completion of various goals.)]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="54">
			<name>Fate (core)</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="39">Justin L.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[A Wild Hunt (Dresdin Files)]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You have been summoned to the throne of the Erlking. It is time for your debt to be repaid. Each of you have traded a favour for power and the chit has been called. Days before All Hallows’ eve the master of the Wild Hunt needs you. The mere thought creeps into your soul and it leaves you in chills. <br /><br /><br />A fatecore game set in the Dresden files]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="55">
			<name>Vampire the Masquerade 5th ed</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="82">Sean M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Bring me his head!]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[WARNING:  this game is not approved for children or young adults. Game will include adult themes, ultra violence and subject matter. <br />It’s never easy in the big easy. The Fangs have been booked as a part of there first tour to play the illustrious Beach on Burbon. You know the gig is going to go sideways when your stopped by a large group of armed men just outside the city limits. What now?]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="56">
			<name>Transformers RPG</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="57">John P.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Transformers RPG is a fan made game by James Kerr that allows players to make up their own transformer… is that a wolf deploying fleas equipped with missiles… and will be divided into two teams the Autobots or Deceptions. A scenario will be provided and each team will have their own mission to complete using their proper programming. Players must roll play their character with the proper assigned (Autobot/Decepticon) programming. For example, an Autobot would be inclined to negotiate to the local government for energy access while a Decepticon would rather break into the local power plant, convert every scrap of energy into energon cubes and leave nothing left but a smoking ruin, burnt and melted beyond all hope of repair.<br /><br />This is a quick and easy game to learn. The game uses a d10 base system for decision making and a d6 for damage. Dice will be provided if players lack their own.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="5" id="57">
			<name>Symbaroum</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="37">Jordan G.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Blight Night]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[During a voyage in Ambria´s border regions, you and your companions make a stop at the inn Jakad´s Heart - a place with a history full of both hope and tragedy. At night the inn is attacked by howling goblins, commanded by the robber baron Nightblade. She is on a desperate hunt for the Water of the Dusk, an artifact said to be able to save a blight-stricken soul - and she is prepared to burn everything to the ground to get what she wants.<br /><br />Will you and your companions survive the siege? Or will you fall to the Blight?<br /><br />Symbaroum is a grim fantasy setting of deep exploration, ancient secrets, and growing darkness in the ageless ruins of Davokar.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="58">
			<name>Fate of the Norns</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="29">James K</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Lo, for you are vikings living in Ragnarok, the end times. Three years ago wolves devoured the sun and moon. The world dwells in darkness and perpetual winter, awaiting the final battle that will end all. Before that happens, however, there are still battles to be fought and treasures won. Who dares risk all to see out the end days in luxury? The RPG system of "Fate of the Norns: Ragnarok" uses the drawing of runes instead of dice rolls. It´s  easy to learn and intuitive in practice. New players make the best vikings! As a Phantasm treat, this game will include sneak-peak content from the "Horn of the Kraken" adventure module set for release next year.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="59">
			<name>Shadow Run</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="5">Bryan M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Paw Patrol]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Genetically modified puppy and human the Paw Patrol are the pinnacle of emergency services in Adventure Bay.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="60">
			<name>Pathfinder 2nd Ed.</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="132">Denis H.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Lastwall has fallen to the undead and orc hordes. The survivors of Lastwall retreat but a select few are chosen to move forward. A daring mission to recover a relic from an ancient ruin before the evil hordes claim it. A Pathfinder 2nd ed introduction game for players of all experience levels.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="61">
			<name>Call of Cthulhu</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="26">Ian M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Boil Water Advisory]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The posters went up this morning, there´s a council meeting tonight. Water´s bad. Again. No doubt the men from Duarock will be singing their same old song. They think because they employ a good chunk of the settlment that we owe them an audience. I wouldn´t be surprised if they had something to do with the water. Tempers are smouldering.. all it would take is one small spark. Boil Water Advisoet is a Call of Cthulhu (7e) scenario for 4-6 players. Pre-generated characters provided. Contains mature/disturbing content.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="62">
			<name>5e Middle Earth</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="85">Alec M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Its been five years since the battle of the five armies. King Bard holds a festival to celebrate the alliance of men, elves and dwarves who defeated the goblin hoards. Men, elves, and other wandering folk travel to lake town from across middle earth. And yet, the forces of shadow are not yet defeated. In the land of Morder the spirit of the dark lord stirs…]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="63">
			<name>Shadowrun 6th ed.</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="31">Jason M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Media Circus]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The newest world player, Spinrad Global, has shaken up the balance within the Corporate Court by their admission into the Big Ten.  One of those upset by the change is Horizon, whose position within the AAA corporations is one of the weakest and this new player is in direct competition.  The runners are hired for a series of defamation attacks, so the new boys know their place.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="64">
			<name>Blades in the Dark</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="133">Dave G.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[At some point, centuries ago a Cataclysm occurred that blacked out the sun but now the only stars you can see are in the demon haunted Void Sea. The Dead walk the earth and it´s only by the grace of Electoplasmic fences to keep them at bay. Welcome to Duskvol, the city where you´ll play as gritty scoundrels trying to scrape a life out of the gutter expanding not just as a party but as a crew.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="65">
			<name>Tiny Wasteland</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="117">Terry B.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[TinyD6 gets apocalyptic! The versatile and minimalist TinyD6 ruleset hits the road in this post-apocalyptic sourcebook. Containing new rules for settlements, vehicles, and mutations, Tiny Wastelands is your trust companion in the blasted landscapes of the near-future.<br />Powered by the TinyD6 engine, with streamlined mechanics that utilize only one to three single six-sided dice on every action, characters that can be written 3x5 notecard, and easy to  understand and teach rules, Tiny Wastelands is here to be your rules-lite waypoint on your lonely apocalyptic road!]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="66">
			<name>Paranoia</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="130">Rob H</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="67">
			<name>D&amp;D 5e</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="119">Nathan D.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[My pleasure is to run for the players a massive 3d printed and foam dungeon for a 5th edition Dungeons and Dragons module.  This module put the players / characters to break out of a necromancer’s jail.  The players character has nothing in common but secrets and have to work together.  This dungeon crawl will be a dungeon craw of epic proportions.   The players/characters have to use their brains, brawn, skill and intelligence to navigate the maze to get out alive or become part of the army of dead.  <br />(each session will include a higher level of characters and will include prizes for completion of various goals.)]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="68">
			<name>Vampire the Masquerade 5th ed</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="82">Sean M.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[Another exciting night]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[WARNING:  this game is not approved for children or young adults. Game will include adult themes, ultra violence and subject matter. <br />After a wild night and a great opportunity the band is preparing to leave New Orleans on their way to the next part of their tour when they are stopped again and “invited” for an audience with a primogen or clan Toreador. You have to know this isn’t going to go well.]]></description>
		</game>
		<game slot="6" id="69">
			<name>Sharp Swords &amp; Sinister Spells</name>
			<gamemaster gmID="37">Jordan G.</gamemaster>
			<title><![CDATA[The Seethers in Darkness]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[You have been hired by a loquacious scholar to accompany him on a quest for a lost ruin in the desert southwest of Zamboula - a ruin no one has ever heard of before.<br /><br />With the offer of virtually anything they may find in addition to a hefty bag of coin, you and your companions have set forth into the desert. The journey through the desert is dangerous, but what you may find may make any danger in the sweeping sands pale in comparison to, the Seethers in Darkness.<br /><br />A Black-Hack inspired RPG in the spirit of the Old School. Fast, Simple and intuitive, this is the Fantasy game you wanted to play when you saw D&D on Television.]]></description>
		</game>
		<boardgame>5 Tribes</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Are You The Trator</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Asteroyds</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Black Friday </boardgame>
		<boardgame>Boxcars</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Cargo Noir</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Caveman</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Cinque Terre</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Dominion</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Dungeoneer</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Dust</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Flux</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Furstenfeld</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Gang of Four</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Loch Ness</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Memoir 44</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Mousquetaires du Roy</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Once Upon a Time</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Pantheon</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Piñata </boardgame>
		<boardgame>Pirates Cove</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Pressure cooker</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Puerto Rico</boardgame>
		<boardgame>RanKing</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Relic Runners</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Shadows over camelot</boardgame>
		<boardgame>The Heavens of Olympus</boardgame>
		<boardgame>Those Pesky Garden Gnomes</boardgame>
		<boardgame>War Hammer Invasion</boardgame>
	</games>
	<gamemasters>
		<gm>
			<name id="1">Adam G.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Adam started roleplaying when he was 8, and has played or GM´d in many systems, including Pathfinder, D20 Modern, Top Secret, Marvel and every version of D&D. He loves character and story driven games, and enjoys creatively interpreting rules whenever pla]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="2">Andrew W.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="3">Andrew Y.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="4">Brian F.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="5">Bryan M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[For more than five years Bryan has been taking childhood memories and warping them into twisted games, that are just too much fun to pass up.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="6">Chris C.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Chris won the story teller of the year award in 2002 and next year will be publishing his first RPG game “Knights of the Hidden Sun”. Whenever you get the chance play with this man his games are too fun to pass up.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="7">Chris M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="8">Chris T.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="9">Cody M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="10">Corey R.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="11">Craig M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Craig is a old school story teller, who has been running games for us every year since the first year of the convention. His game are quite fun, well worth checking out.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="12">Darcy B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="13">Dave M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="14">David E.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="15">David L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="16">David W.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Gaming started for me in grade two (2) when I played a mage that was magically teleported to the front of a roman legion. So I fireballed them. My GM (also in grade 2) wasn´t to good with area calculations or math in general. So I vanquished the whole le]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="17">Duncan J</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="18">Ed Greenwood</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Ed Greenwood is the creator of the Forgotten Realms fantasy world, which became the setting for his home D&D game in 1975. Play still continues in this long-running campaign, and Ed also keeps busy producing Realmslore for various TSR publications. Ed]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="19">Erik W.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Erik was excited by an ad in Analog Magazine for something called Gamma World. The idea that playing pieces on a board could constitute a mechanism for enacting stories caught his imagination and it hasn´t let him go. When not gaming, he teaches secondary school in Toronto and blogs about obscure aspects of theatre history, theory, and literature.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="20">Erica M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="21">Francis B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="22">George B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="23">Graham R.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="24">Greg S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="25">Greig A.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="26">Ian M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="27">James</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="28">James A.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="29">James K</name>
			<description><![CDATA[In 1987 James Kerr placed a peanut butter sandwich in his parent´s VCR and was transported to a magical world where he was taught by long-dead druids the secrets of dice rolling, community, and dungeon mastership. Returning to this world he has been playi]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="30">Jason B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[is a deviant mind of the highest caliber who has been running LARP for Phantasm for 7 years.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="31">Jason M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[is a two-time winner of the Hammer of Plot and overall awesome human being.  He is a GM that is all about keeping his players entertained.  His material is light on planning and heavy on over-the-top action.  If you attend Phantasm, you owe it to yourself]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="32">Jayson P.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="33">Jean Marc S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Jean-Marc has been coming out to the con for a while now and always is a con favourite. He runs a number of games of his own creation like \"Fallout\".]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="34">Jeff C.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="35">Jon Mark J.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[If we could find a way to harness this man’s energy we would solve the energy crisis hands down. Jon Mark runs a high energy game full of drama where hero exemplify what it is to be a hero.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="36">Jon Moore</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Jon has been playing and running games since he was 12 and purchased the D&D Red Box in a whim, over 20 years ago.  Moving quickly from D&D to Rifts, he owns a metric ton of all manner of Palladium Source material. Now well-dedicated to the GURPS system,]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="37">Jordan G.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[The Self-Proclaimed Overlord Game Master of Mississauga, Jordan has carved out a niche with his expansive library of over a hundred games; If you enjoy fast, light and fun RPGs you´ll not be disappointed at his table.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="38">Joshua K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="39">Justin L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="40">Lawrence M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Lawrence we got from Orion, and we’re quite glad to have him. He runs D20 Cthulu for us, and puts a ton of effort into it.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="41">Lawrence W.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Lawrence Whitaker has been role-playing since the ice sheets started to recede and claims he has a genuine knuckle-bone d20 - although this might not be true. What is true is that Lawrence has over 25 years of experience as a player, GM and games writer.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="42">Malcolm S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Malcolm Sheppard has been writing and designing roleplaying games for about a decade, beginning with material for White Wolf´s classic Mage: The Ascension line. Since then he´s gone to work on the current World of Darkness (Mage, Changeling and Geist),]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="43">Matt Clark</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="44">Mike C.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="45">Mike K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="46">Mike M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="47">Nick S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Nick puts a ton of effort and play testing into his games, its great to see a table get drawn into one of his woven tales.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="48">Paige W.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="49">Paul G.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="50">Jay L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="51">Peter L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Peter L is a old school GM with a new school feel. He runs great games that focus on fun and letting the PC´s be hero´s who can do cool things.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="52">Rebecca Z.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="53">Robert H</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="54">Roland K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="55">Steve C.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Steve runs these great games that focus around the players and build on their actions. If you get a chance you have to try some of the games of Steve\’s own design, they are pretty fun.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="56">Steve E.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Steve has the largest RPG collection I’ve ever seen. He loves to dive into new games and settings. When he runs a game he focuses entirely on the story and player’s enjoyment, the rules come second.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="57">John P.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="58">Michel L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="59">Frank O</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="60">David R.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="61">Nathan D.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[I believe in stories because they define who we are.  An avid rpg’s since the first red book to the latest 5th edition, I bring decades of experience in storytelling to the table.  An avid 3d printer for the last 5 years, I bring over 500 3d printed terrain and scatter to the game.   I love telling stories in a visual and dramatic way.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="62">Derek H.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Derek has always been gaming in some sort of capacity. He picked up D&D in 1980 and started to DM in 1983 and has not stopped playing since. He´s played Traveller, GURPS and all kinds of wierd wonderful RPGs. While still playing D&D/Pathfinder to this day]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="63">Jared K</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="64">Eddy K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="65">Greg L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="66">Kat J.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="67">Mark R.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="68">Pathfinder Society</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="69">Jacob H.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="70">Trevor L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="71">Peterborough X-Wing Squadron</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="72">James L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Been away for a couple of years.  I am happy to be running a few events again for Phantasm. I am looking to try and get Palladium Books some recognition again as here in Peterborough it really is not known well at all.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="73">Bryan C.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="74">Tom T.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="75">Jaymz L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="76">Shawn L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[I am currently a Press Ganger for Privateer Press, which is to say that I am a volunteer gameplay coordinator for Privateer Press Products. I´ve been doing this officially for just under a year, but have been demoing Privateer Press Products for three. I have been plying RPGs since I was 12 with an old copy of 1st edition Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, and have played multiple RPGs over the past 23 years both as a PC and as a Game Master. I expanded into Miniature war gaming with Warhammer 40,00 with an Eldar and a Space Wolves Army. I decided that after surviving the supposed end of the world of 2012, I felt that a great reward for my survivability would be learning to play a new game. I started playing Hordes and then moved to Include Warmachine. Recently I have started to add the iron Kingdoms RPG to my repertoire of games supported and have had a fantastic time hosting and playing this RPG.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="77">Matthew K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="78">TBA</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="79">Scott B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="80">Stu M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="81">Jeff K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="82">Sean M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="83">Andrew V.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[Gamer since the early 80’s and designer since the early 90’s. Best known works are the Fate of the Norns line of games: Ragnarok, Gulveig and Vigridr.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="84">Dan K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="85">Alec M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="86">Jessika E.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="87">Dennis H.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[I have an extensive background running a wide range of game systems. Starting with AD&D in the early 80´s and branching off in to other systems such as Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay, Gurps, Rolemaster, Rifts, Recon, Palladium, Shadowrun, Star Wars d6(west end) and many others. I have DM every version of D&D and I am currently the Local coordinator for D&D 5e for the Belleville area. I have run games at a variety of cons over the years Knight March, Orion, and of course Phantasm." I prefer to run games then play in them smile emoticon]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="88">Eugene F.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="89">Jeff P.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="90">Lance S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="91">Paul K.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="92">Anthony U.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="93">Rolando M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="94">Irene M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="95">Ian P.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="96">Dale D.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="97">Derek M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="98">Xavier D.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="99">Dave G. </name>
			<description><![CDATA[Ever since one kid brought the 3rd Ed starter box to school one day in 2000, my make belief had a framework that make it so much better, more fun and good deal more Epic.

With the new publishing/Kickstarter funding renewal for there are more games with more amazing mechanics than I could ever imagine.

Though little of that seems to matter because in the end the villains always seem to be Drow, Cults of the King in Yellow, or Mindflayers, just done in so many ways!

I have probably several dozen games on my shelf I´ve never tried and it´s only with an adventurous group of players (with at least semi consistent schedules) that we´ll get to see them all and discover all they have to offer.

I´m looking to immerse my players in the story and have three priorities in this order: fun, storyline, rules as written.]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="100">Adventurers League</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="101">Adam M.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="102">Rob S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="103">Rob H.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="104">Allison S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="105">Jessica F.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="106">Jessica E.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="107">Joe N.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="108">Jon-Mark J.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="109">Kerri F.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="110">Malcom S.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="111">Matthew D.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="112">Wil G.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="113">Greg N.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="114">Jeff &amp; Dave</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="115">Dave C.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="116">David C.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="117">Terry B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="118">Richard B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="119">Nathan D.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="120">Rob E.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="121">Ken B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="122">Wil</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="123">Jamieson B.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="124">James H.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="125">Chris L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="126">Michael V.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="127">Elias A.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="128">Allan N.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="129">Andrew L.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="130">Rob H</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="131">Jason Mel.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="132">Denis H.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
		<gm>
			<name id="133">Dave G.</name>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
		</gm>
	</gamemasters>
</schedule>
